<resources>
    <string name="app_name">signify</string>
    <string name="default_web_client_id">480370863906-8deqtn8nq63qk01efb5pudici2c805ek.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>
    <string name="help_home_screen">Here you can practice your sign language, with feedback through your camera.
Make sure to check your daily quest to learn a new letter every day.
You’ll also find exercises at the bottom to challenge yourself at varying levels of difficulty.</string>
    <string name="help_profile_screen">Here, you can change your settings and customize your profile. You’ll also get to add your friends to learn together. You’ll find a recap of your progress in the statistics board.</string>
    <string name="description_challenge">Here you can challenge your friends to sign language face-offs.</string>
    <string name="graphs_history">Graphs and statistics for the challenges</string>
    <string name="button_uri_string">
        https://nerdish.io/topics/what-you-should-know-about-sign-language/
    </string>
    <string name="help_asl_recognition">Practice your ASL hand gestures using the camera and see real-time feedback.</string>
    <string name="help_offline_mode">You are currently offline. Use the login button to return online.</string>
    <string-array name="real_words">
        <item>cat</item>
        <item>dog</item>
        <item>bat</item>
        <item>hat</item>
        <item>rat</item>
        <item>sun</item>
        <item>fan</item>
        <item>run</item>
        <item>cup</item>
        <item>pen</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="real_words_hard">
        <item>apple</item>
        <item>grapes</item>
        <item>banana</item>
        <item>orange</item>
        <item>pencil</item>
        <item>guitar</item>
        <item>flower</item>
        <item>window</item>
        <item>horse</item>
        <item>planet</item>
        <item>bridge</item>
        <item>ladder</item>
        <item>rabbit</item>
        <item>garden</item>
        <item>button</item>
        <item>silver</item>
        <item>pillow</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="real_sentences">
        <item>The cat sits on the mat</item>
        <item>Birds fly across the sky</item>
        <item>She walks to the park</item>
        <item>It rains on summer days</item>
        <item>The stars shine at night</item>
        <item>Dogs bark in the yard</item>
        <item>The sun rises every day</item>
        <item>A child plays with toys</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="tip_a">Tips: Close your hand, put your thumb to the left, and direct it to the left.</string>
    <string name="tip_b">Tips: Extend all fingers straight up. Place your thumb across your palm. Fingers are straight and close together.</string>
    <string name="tip_c">Tips: Fingers and thumb are curved to form a C shape.</string>
    <string name="tip_d">Tips: Extend your index finger up while touching your thumb to the tip of your middle finger. Other fingers are slightly curved.</string>
    <string name="tip_e">Tips: Curl your fingers down over your thumb, forming an E shape with the fingertips near the thumb.</string>
    <string name="tip_f">Tips: Touch the tip of your thumb to the tip of your index finger to form an O shape. The other fingers are extended and spread out.</string>
    <string name="tip_g">Tips: Hold your thumb and index finger parallel and close to each other, while the other fingers are folded down.</string>
    <string name="tip_h">Tips: Extend your index and middle fingers, holding them together. Other fingers are curled down.</string>
    <string name="tip_i">Tips: Raise your pinky finger up, keeping all other fingers down, including the thumb.</string>
    <string name="tip_j">Tips: Move your pinky finger downwards in a slight curve, as if drawing the letter J in the air.</string>
    <string name="tip_k">Tips: Extend your index and middle fingers apart, with your thumb touching the middle finger. The other fingers are curled down.</string>
    <string name="tip_l">Tips: Form an L shape by extending your index finger up and your thumb out to the side, keeping the other fingers curled down.</string>
    <string name="tip_m">Tips: Tuck your thumb under your index, middle, and ring fingers, with only the pinky finger showing outside.</string>
    <string name="tip_n">Tips: Tuck your thumb under your index and middle fingers, with the other fingers resting down.</string>
    <string name="tip_o">Tips: Curve all fingers and the thumb to form an O shape.</string>
    <string name="tip_p">Tips: Point your index and middle fingers down, keeping them apart, with the thumb supporting them. The other fingers are curled down.</string>
    <string name="tip_q">Tips: Point your thumb and index finger down in an L shape. The rest of the fingers are curled down.</string>
    <string name="tip_r">Tips: Cross your index and middle fingers, holding them together, while the other fingers are curled down.</string>
    <string name="tip_s">Tips: Make a fist with your thumb resting over the other fingers.</string>
    <string name="tip_t">Tips: Make a fist with your thumb tucked between your index and middle fingers.</string>
    <string name="tip_u">Tips: Hold your index and middle fingers up and close together, with the other fingers curled down.</string>
    <string name="tip_v">Tips: Hold your index and middle fingers up and apart in a V shape, with the other fingers curled down.</string>
    <string name="tip_w">Tips: Hold your index, middle, and ring fingers up, spreading them out, with the other fingers curled down.</string>
    <string name="tip_x">Tips: Curl your index finger, pointing it up, while the other fingers are folded down. Your thumb rests near the index finger.</string>
    <string name="tip_y">Tips: Extend your pinky and thumb out to the sides, with the other fingers folded down.</string>
    <string name="tip_z">Tips: Move your index finger to trace a Z shape in the air.</string>
    <string name="unauthenticated_error">You must be logged in to access this feature</string>
    <integer name="scroll_offset">8</integer>"
    <string name="friends_requests">Requests</string>
    <string name="friends">Friends</string>
    <string name="pref_name">theme_prefs</string>
    <string name="pref_key_is_dark_theme">is_dark_theme</string>
    <string name="pref_name_language">en</string>
    <string name="pref_key_is_french">is_french</string>
</resources>